coinb.ink 2018-05-17

# Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by [http://coinb.ink](http://coinb.ink/) **.**  

At [ **Coinbink**](http://coinb.ink/) ** ** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by[ **Coinbink**](http://coinb.ink/) and how it is used. 

Log Files

Like many other Web sites,[ **Coinbink**](http://coinb.ink/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

Cookies and Web Beacons 

[**Coinbink**](http://coinb.ink/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

DoubleClick DART Cookie 

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [ **Coinbink**](http://coinb.ink/).

.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [ **Coinbink**](http://coinb.ink/) ** ** and other sites on the Internet. 

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....

Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [ **Coinbink**](http://coinb.ink/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

[**Coinbink**](http://coinb.ink/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  **[Coinbink](http://coinb.ink/)'s** privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy establishes the terms in the Coinbink and protects the information that is provided by the users when using your website. This company is committed to the security of the data of its users. When we ask you to fill in the fields of personal information with which you can be identified, we do so by ensuring that they are only used in accordance with the terms of this document. However, this Privacy Policy may change over time to be updated so we recommend and emphasize continually reviewing this page to ensure that you agree to the changes.

**Information that is collected**

Our website collect personal information such as: Name, contact information such as email address and demographic information. Also, when necessary, information can be requested to process an order or make a delivery or billing.

**Use of collected information**

Our website uses the information in order to provide the best possible service, to maintain a register of users, orders in case of application, and to improve our products and services. Emails may be periodically sent through our site with special offers, new products and other public information that you consider relevant to you or that may provide some benefit, these emails are sent to the address you provided and were canceled in any moment

Coinbink is firmly committed to meeting the commitment to keep your information safe. We use the most advanced systems and constantly update to ensure that there is no unauthorized access.

**Biscuits**

A cookie refers to a file that is sent in order to request permission to store on your computer, all accepted file is created and the cookie serves to have information about web traffic, and also facilitate visits to a web Recurrent Another function that Have the cookies is that with the web can recognize you individually and therefore provide the best personalized service on your website.

Our website uses cookies to be able to identify the pages that are visited and their frequency. This information is used for statistical analysis and after the information is permanently deleted. You can remove cookies at any time from your computer. However, cookies help to provide better service to websites, you do not have access to information from your computer or from you, unless you want it and proportion directly. You can accept or deny the use of cookies, however most browsers are cookies. You can also change the settings of your computer to declare cookies. If you decline, you may not be able to use some of our services.

**Links to Third Parties**

This web site may contain other sites that may be of interest to you. Once you are in these links and leave our page, there is no control over the site that is redirected and therefore are not responsible for the terms of privacy or protection of your data on those other third sites. Such sites are subject to their own privacy policies so it is recommended that customers know that you agree with them.

**Control of your personal information**

At any time you may restrict the collection or use of the personal information that is provided to our website. Each time you request to fill out a form, such as the user registration, you can check or uncheck the option to receive information by email. In case you have marked the option to receive our advertising bulletin you can cancel it at any time.

This company did not sell, did not distribute the personal information that is collected without its consent, except that the sea required by a judge with a court order.

Coinbink reserves the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time.
